FANSUB GROUP AZALIA PRESENTS
Worked on the series:
Lily, Tiramisu, Biryulka, Host, February
How did I become
queen
All characters are fictitious
and the events shown are fiction.
Did Hong find out anything?
Apparently, Kim Byunin guessed
that the piece of fabric he found was from the palace.
He's getting closer.
Let's hurry up too.
-We are learning not to attack.
-Is it true?
What's wrong with you?
Losing your mind is not in your rules.
I've been holding back for too long
I'm tired of waiting.
Dangerous Liaisons
Episode 8
Hold it.
Well, let's go.
Did you go hunting?
As they say: "Rest..."
"Rest and wait until they get tired."
While I rest, my enemies get tired.
You're right.
But how did you catch a hare without a bow?
The bow made my hands and fingers hurt.
I'm sure it wasn't invented for hunting.
but to torture people.
Although, if your hands and fingers hurt after it,
then for hunting people - just right.
In any case, the animals are easier to trap.
It's dangerous for you to hunt with just the two of you.
The guard must guard you wherever you go.
Next time I'll take it with me.
By the way, are you still the head of the king’s guard?
When the queen's father gets better,
I will relinquish this responsibility.
Exactly.
For your health -
accept.
Everything is fine. No need.
Don't refuse me.
This is a gift from the king.
Got you.
Did you hear - the queen woke up?
Is it true?
How is she feeling?
Fortunately, Her Majesty is healthy.
She overcame her illness.
What a relief.
I must see Her Majesty.
God.
Now is not the time for visits.
Since the queen is better,
we avoided the worst outcome.
I'll look for the ledger myself.
I'll go with you.
This will only make them wary.
Keep an eye on everything that happens in the palace.
The weather is nice today.
You won't catch it!
It smelled like spring.
Will you marry me?
I may not have come out with my face,
but I have a goat.
Well, I don't know.
Your Majesty!
I wanted her to come back so bad.
And only her memories returned.
Previously, they appeared as outbreaks here and there.
Every time I had a headache and a ringing in my ears.
But this time the memories appeared without special effects.
Hongyeon, you will be 19 this year.
But your name is not Hongyong.
Hong is a surname, and your name is Yeon.
My sense of smell.
Smells help you remember.
But why
Am I that good at playing?
You have played the gayageum since childhood.
Your memory is back
Here the talents have awakened.
What a crap.
As soon as I was a vegetable, everything went wrong.
Stop.
Why did the voice in my head become female?
What am I,
lost your voice?
What are you talking about?
I can hear you perfectly.
The strength has returned to my fingers
but the voice disappeared. Just like
in "The Little Mermaid"?
Find out so that there is no doubt about the words of the witness,
who sold arsenic to the court lady Khan
as a poison for mice, and how the poison got into the king's kitchen.
I have business with the head of the Detective Department.
How strange.
The palace has always been big
but today it is especially huge and empty.
Her Majesty is coming.
Am I...
I agreed to give the Queen Mother some time.
-What?
-That's the order
courtyard.
For now we'll wait.
But have all the evidence ready
to use them at any time.
Keep them secret.
Maybe we were able to piece together the whole picture,
but the queen mother may be related
with those who want to harm the queen.
If we leave her alone,
Her Majesty may be in danger again.
People who want to harm the queen?
The Queen admitted that she wanted to kill herself by throwing herself into the pond.
This time her health failed her.
What are we talking about?
She became a target as soon as she crossed the threshold of the palace.
This is what worries me.
Understand.
Organize a meeting without a king -
it's still a headache.
I'll go.
Has something happened to His Majesty?
He went to the queen.
Really?
Benin!
Didn't know you were here.
You can continue.
It's good for you to get home.
It's midday
Why are you sending him home?
I didn't sleep all night, so I got it wrong.
What were you working on if you confuse day and night?
I was on a secret mission all night.
I suffered such fear.
So, did you learn anything?
Benin, I'm lost.
Fell in love with a woman I shouldn't have.
And who is she?
For some reason the palace is especially empty today,
empty in my heart too.
I kept wondering what was wrong with me.
And now in the palace there is only
one woman.
Her Majesty.
I think I've fallen in love with the queen.
-What?
-How could I fall in love with my sister?
This is against the law on incest.
We are from the same family.
It's the same as incest.
As if this were not enough, she is a stranger’s woman and married to the king.
I'm crazy.
No, that's putting it mildly
I lost all my brains on the road.
Even if you forget about all this,
what is more important -
she is much older than me.
Is this normal?
Are you still worried about her age?!
Why are you yelling at me?
You are talking outright nonsense.
Sorry.
I won't say anything more.
No, it's okay.
Sorry for yelling.
You never once raised your voice at me,
and I never got angry.
You have changed a lot since your appointment.
Yes, it's up to my neck.
I wasn't angry at you.
How did you even come to this conclusion?
Everything around reminds me of her.
How she held the Queen's umbrella
how she stayed next to her,
how she ran with a decoction for Her Majesty.
All I can think about is Hong Young, the Queen's lady-in-waiting.
If you think about Hong Young,
why did you decide that you fell in love with the queen?
Have you forgotten who I am?
I am the 16th descendant and first son
for 3 generations in the family of judges.
I'm Kim Hwan.
Can I fall in love
some court lady?
Therefore, I am sure that in my heart...
Did I fall in love with a court lady?!
Good luck to you on the thorny path of love.
Initial Instruction for Children
Cho Hwajin
Your Highness.
Where is the king?
He went to the queen's house.
Why so suddenly?
The Queen regained consciousness.
He wants to take the opportunity to search her house.
Are you hurt?
It's OK.
Then I will also visit the queen.
To what do I owe this pleasure?
Skinny
thick,
high
and low.
All different sizes and heights.
But they all have one thing in common.
This
your eyes.
You have the best vision and aim.
You are the shooters I handpicked.
And I have average height and weight.
What type am I?
You'll be slow-witted.
And that's what I called your squad.
Les Misérables.
You were sent to the front line,
because they were considered nonentities.
But with these guns
you will become the best warriors of Joseon.
Like me.
A gun can take a life.
But also
might save her.
Line up five in a row to shoot.
It's troublesome, but I have to save this country.
Fire!
I came to pick up what I need.
The first is a phoenix hairpin.
Phoenix hairpin?
A gift for the queen?
If only for the queen,
I would ask for Saniywon.
I don't need a gold royal phoenix clip.
I need the one made of jade.
But according to royal etiquette, only the queen
can wear phoenix hairpins.
Exactly.
And the second thing I need is...
I knew it. She wants to seduce the king there.
Quicker. We must finish with a bullet.
Yes. Quicker.
Before the queen tells him the secret.
There is one difference between me and the little mermaid.
She got legs for her vote, and I got arms.
Surprise after surprise.
So will I lose myself drop by drop?
If I stay here
this bastard, Director Khan,
will get everything he wants.
I can accuse his ancestors of treason,
hunt down the Khans and destroy the entire family.
I will destroy three generations of Khans,
so that they could not conceive him.
But to which clan do they belong?
Why does her mood constantly change?
Are you all from the Namsadan troupe here?
Where do these skills come from?
For Joseon women, this is nothing.
This is the only way to look behind the walls.
I didn't know what the deep meaning was.
And it's true. After living here for a week, I realized
that the life of a Joseon woman is much harder than I expected.
And by the way, I’m also the queen here.
But if I can take bloody revenge...
Let's go.
Everything will be fine if you don't smell.
Memories will not return.
And my voice will return.
From this day forward I will live for revenge.
And for this I need power.
Hong Young.
What, as a queen, must I do to gain unprecedented power?
I know the best way to gain power.
Which one?
Producing an heir will give you the most power.
Production?
What kind of word is this inhumane?
Exactly.
For me, the super-powerful Sunwon.
Who is Sunwon?
Such a village name.
Queen Sunwon. She's the Dowager Queen.
Hong Young, if I want to impress her,
-what do I need...
-Give birth to an heir. Exactly.
I'll get her a gift. What could you come up with?
Something small and shiny
expensive and beautiful.
Wait a minute.
This smell...
Memories come back, come back...
This repository is called Heaven. What's in the backyard is the Earth.
And what's next to the guest room - Black?
Yes. Your father accumulated wealth while you were away.
All storage facilities are full.
Sky, Earth, Black...
If you think about all the warehouses in Joseon, not just these...
Your family had to use all the Chinese characters.
Oh, my little eyes!
Look, I was born with a golden spoon in my mouth.
This.
And this.
And besides them,
pack everything else.
Everything else?
Let's take everything and return to the palace.
Your father will have a blow.
From this day forward, I will be the Queen of Lobbying.
Your Majesty.
The king has arrived.
Why is this still necessary?
I'll be back soon myself.
Tell me to let him wait for me in the palace.
What are you saying?
I need to show my devotion to grandma.
And stay away from the king.
What are you doing?
I need to clearly show which side I'm on.
Here I grabbed it.
Why is he in full dress?
All these royal families are such show-offs.
Show the king your respect.
Everything is fine.
So, I nominate Soyeon from the Kim family as queen.
Congratulations on your election.
Picked it up on the way here.
My queen.
You blushed. And you breathe faster.
Are you having difficulty breathing again?
My face is fine and I'm breathing normally.
I just overate this morning.
Go away, Soyeon.
Get out of me... That is, get out of this body immediately.
What are you doing?
I have nowhere else to go.
Is this how you destroy flowers or your body?
Hey, why do you keep...
- That's enough already.
-Get lost.
I won't give it away, he's mine!
I didn't know you'd like them so much.
I didn't say I liked it.
I just think it's better to stay here
than living in a corpse.
How do you manage
waking up more and more strange?
I'm not the only one who's weird here. You have a lot of weird things yourself.
“Picked them up on the way here”? Seriously?
Have they been driving such a blizzard for a couple of centuries already?
But I actually picked them up along the way.
Well, yes, of course, great, bravo.
This is true.
I really believe it, I believe it.
The king never lies.
-Well, yes, well, yes, yeah, yeah.
-What's wrong with you?
- How is that possible? What is it?
-Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
You blessed our humble abode with your visit.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Please stand up.
I had to check on my queen and make sure everything was okay.
How are you doing? Are you okay?
Yes, sure.
Let's go in.
-Certainly.
-Great.
My King, enjoy your hospitality.
And I need to prepare to return to the palace.
- Let's go.
-What? Are you leaving already?
Do you want to go back to the palace today?
I'm recovering quickly.
Even so,
You just recovered.
Father is right.
There is no need to rush, you need to fully recover.
I'm worried that the courtyard will fight without me.
Everything is calm in the courtyard.
Calmer than when you were in the palace.
Much calmer.
Sorry.
I tried my best
but it seems you are unhappy with me.
-Yes I...
-You're already used to the palace.
and spend time with dad
you don't like it at all.
God.
I concentrated
on duty as queen
and didn’t think about your feelings at all, father.
I will return to the palace tomorrow.
If so, I invite you two to the guest house.
I fell for the trick.
Let's go.
What fly bit her?
There is a task for you.
Bring me something that shouldn't exist.
From a hiding place in the queen's father's chambers.
Yes.
I'm glad to see you here together.
So happy that I don’t mind dying.
I should have visited you earlier.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing to apologize for.
It's enough for me to hear
how you love each other.
My queen is so different from other women
I was always interested to see where she grew up.
This is the place.
I raised her alone, without a mother,
so I tried especially hard
give her all the care she needs.
It must have been hard.
Well, no, not at all.
The Queen did a good job herself
from a young age.
Yes, I've heard that.
However, she is so strong and independent,
that he doesn't share his feelings with me.
Am I that stupid?
Or is it impossible to understand what is on a woman's mind?
It's terribly difficult for me to understand her.
God, it's definitely not due to lack of intelligence.
All men find it difficult to understand women.
They are as complex as the Buddha's teachings.
Don't try to understand.
Marital relationships are filled with misunderstandings.
What does it mean?
No misunderstandings
people wouldn't get married at all.
I want to know everything about you.
Stop it.
I want to see the house
in which she grew up.
Can I do this?
I'll be happy to take a walk with the Queen and catch up.
This is an ordinary tradesman's house.
Nothing special
but I'll be happy to show you everything here.
Then go together.
The Queen must come with me.
We didn't see each other for one night,
but I miss you even when I look at you.
You've got something stuck.
This is a mole.
It seemed to me that today you are different.
You must come with us.
Shall we go?
Wait. The two of you take your time.
I'll check if all the rooms are cleaned.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
Distance, don't you remember?
The longer I think, the more meaningful the phrase becomes.
Even if we don't agree on everything,
we can coexist happily.
This is wonderful, right?
Embracing our differences
and overcoming them.
Have you become a philosopher?
Where has “distancing” taken you?
Oh, exactly. After all, you are a politician.
You saw how happy my father was when he saw us together.
I'm trying to be a good son-in-law, help me.
God.
All the servants look unusually strong
and dexterous.
They know the layout of the house like the back of their hand.
-Let's go.
-Certainly.
I'm glad I asked you to show everything here.
Of course, there are very valuable things here.
So. Here, for example.
White porcelain and folding screen.
It wasn't easy for me to get them.
Can I take a closer look?
Yes, sure.
Look here...
There is nothing interesting on the other side.
Even the reverse side of a work of art looks exquisite.
Be careful, queen.
-What's happened?
-To your dazzling beauty
even the bees flock.
-Bees?
-Where?
-There.
- Be careful.
-There are no bees here.
-Where? Where are they?
-God.
-Where are they?
- Looks like they've flown away.
My queen, what can you say about the screen?
Strong brush strokes, great landscape painting.
Darling, I guess.
You are probably afraid that valuables may be stolen.
I'm sure you have plenty of guards to guard them at night.
No, I don't have a guard.
These days it's more like hired guards
will steal what they are supposed to protect.
While?
I have trained several servants who work for me
whom I trust
they perform guard duties.
It's cheaper than hiring trained guards.
You are very wise.
And how many such servants do you have?
This is classified information.
Then you don't have to tell me.
However my queen remains here
I'm worried.
My queen?
26-27 somewhere.
There can be no secrets between us.
You have enough people to protect a 9-room estate.
Your words calmed me down.
I doubted whether you had any old books,
dated two centuries earlier.
Money alone is not enough to own such books.
You will be very surprised.
Is it true? Surprised?
On your way to the library you will see
the umbrella pine tree I cherished.
The shape of its crown resembles a phoenix.
I heard that if you plant a tree,
a queen will appear in the family.
The sign worked.
Almost there. Follow me.
Damn pine.
This winter I will use it for firewood.
Glad to hear your rude and arrogant remarks again.
At first, when you changed,
I thought you were abusing your power.
Thought you were with your family
trying to trample me.
Misunderstanding.
And you just...
What?
Just arrogant.
I come from a wealthy family. I can afford it.
I wasn't kidding when I said I wanted to understand you.
I want to know
how a woman from a noble family became like you in Joseon.
Don't even try.
A woman like me cannot exist in Joseon.
"I am the most powerful in this world."
You're definitely arrogant.
Hurt.
Return of the king to the throne after overthrow
What happened to you?
Nothing.
God.
His health has deteriorated due to worry about you.
I'll call for help to take you inside.
Keep an eye on him until I get back.
What are you doing?
Did you see a ghost?
The smell of damp...
Save me.
It's my fault. I am to blame for the death.
In this well...
Your Majesty.
Help the king. Hurry up.
Main concubine?
What's happened?
You turned pale.
Really...
Father, escort the king inside.
It seems the concubine has come to talk to me.
I came here concerned about your health.
But it seems the king is feeling bad.
What happened?
I didn't sleep last night.
For a second I felt dizzy.
I will accompany you to the guest house.
The doctor has already been called.
I don't need a doctor.
I'll rest and everything will be fine.
-Hurry up. Help His Majesty.
-Fine.
Carefully.
Be careful.
You can go.
Would you like to lie down?
No.
I'll sit and rest for a while.
I heard you don't remember much about your time in Hanyang,
you were very young then.
I was still a child then.
Due to an unpleasant event, I left Hanyang.
I don't remember much.
What a relief.
That is, I wanted to say that it is better to let go
bad memories.
I think so too.
This fool opened Pandora's box.
You are not what they say.
But I still doubted it.
Don't worry. I didn't tell him anything.
Isn't that why you're here?
So what do you want?
You didn't just lure him here for nothing.
I really wanted to get along with you.
You were my last hope.
While I wanted you
I could be myself.
But I found out the truth about you.
The truth?
About you being a fake Kim So-yeon.
you called me
fake?
I remembered everything.
It's more like you showed your true colors.
I'll help you, since
with you my hormones were raging.
Confess everything to the king.
It will be painful for him to learn about this from someone else.
Are you threatening me?
I heard you clearly.
Your Majesty, I brought you some light snacks.
How difficult it is to reach her.
She's holding on to a complicated relationship
I'm confused myself. Spoiled girl.
Come in.
Your Majesty.
Have you talked to her yet?
Leave us for a while.
Are you okay?
Sorry for making you worry about nothing.
No need for formalities, we are alone here.
Your Majesty,
the queen made a full recovery.
Let's go back to the palace.
I can't.
I need to study something.
Something to study?
What exactly?
Sorry.
Forgive me my bad manners.
I have prepared a room for you. Let me take you.
I must return to the palace.
Well, I'll wait for you at the palace.
Take care of yourself.
His grandfather was Prince Eunong.
He was accused of treason, exiled and executed.
His father was Prince Jeongye.
Lived in exile with his father,
fell ill and died.
His grandmother and aunt were killed because of their baptism,
and half-brother Lee Won-kyung
killed for treason.
This is not a TV show.
Why did everyone in his family die?
Why are you looking at me like that?
How do I look?
Like I'm a pathetic little dog.
No need to smile. I'm worried about you.
Apparently, therefore, early education only harms.
What useless knowledge!
You. What do you want from me?
Why did you stick to me?
What do I want from you?
If the queen suddenly interferes with our plans,
I will personally behead her.
I want you not to interfere with me.
You don't have to help me. Just
don't become my enemy.
And you have a trained eye.
I may not be able to help much with anything,
but as an enemy I am terrible.
I'll grab hold of you and won't let go.
Your Majesty!
Kim Byonin has come to see you.
How many guests do I have today?
They come to me like they go to a restaurant.
Are you okay?
I'd say too good.
Any problems?
Why is the head of the Detective Department here?
While the king and queen are here,
It should be like a palace here.
Your Majesty.
From now on, you are under the protection of the Detective Department.
I brought the royal guards with me, you have nothing to worry about.
Then you will be protected by the royal guard,
and we will protect the queen.
Are there too many people?
Then you can recall the royal guards.
You are not in your right place.
To protect us
look around, not at us.
Apparently, my destiny is to be surrounded by those who look at me.
Who is this?
Everything is fine?
Wait, this...
Why is he here?
Do you know him?
Come to your senses, wake up.
Save me, Benin.
Benin?
Why did he try to attack the queen?
She could have gotten hurt.
Go away, woman! Get out of this body!
-Leave.
-Queen.
What did this chatterbox forget here?
What were you thinking?
I really wanted to see her face.
Right. I...
In Joseon I...
Mrs. Hong Young.
queen.
He wanted to see your maid.
Does he really not recognize me like this?
You said you would protect the queen
but they only showed their vulnerability.
Why are you so unhappy?
Detective department?
Are you up to something?
What could I be up to?
Recently, many warehouses have been robbed in the capital.
-And what?
-We need to strengthen security measures.
But if you prevent it,
is it possible that you make money from this?
Take it easy, despite his past,
he is still the king.
Let's find out today.
I'm very glad.
I myself am a skilled warrior, and I have the right instincts,
it wouldn't cost me much
difficulty dodging blows.
I wanted to discuss something with you
that's why I asked to come.
Yes? That's it.
I also have one request for you.
I don't know if it's possible to ask for this.
What kind of request?
Won't you blow on my bruises?
Even your breath is fragrant.
Now I'm completely confused, what now
I'm experiencing.
There's only one way to know for sure.
Sorry in advance.
But I have to find out.
What are you doing here?
Sorry for not recognizing such an important husband.
What kind of smile is this?
A smile with which I beg for forgiveness.
My breath is fragrant, and my smile is even more beautiful.
And you know a lot about drinking.
You can handle alcohol quite well yourself.
Of course, that's why I'm the king.
Have they already drunk that much?
Well, now it's that time.
-ERV.
-ERV?
Time of the dog and the wolf.
The hour when all the veils are torn off,
those who coexisted peacefully during the day,
they squabble like dogs and wolves.
Answer me as husband to husband.
You're nothing
don't you have feelings for my queen?
Only feelings for her
can explain your hostility towards me.
There are all sorts of donkeys in the world.
There are those who themselves
they don’t feel anything for the virgin,
but they can’t allow her to be with anyone else.
Am I the bossy ass?
The best of women is next to you,
and you don't notice it.
Like eating a donkey, a complete fool.
Take it easy, guys.
I'm not interested in any of you.
You're lying.
I know you like me.
Look into my eyes.
Or are you...
A wise king should be complacent,
but victory is mine.
It's funny.
It's time for you to repay my kindness.
So we met again.
Although I tried to stay away
so as not to bother you again.
Why, Queen Mother, you don’t bother me at all.
I have a gift for you.
This is...
If anyone deserves to be near the king, it's you.
The title of Her Majesty suits you much better.
What were you looking at, child?
Admired the reflection of the moon in the waters.
Within the walls of the palace you can hear many scary stories.
About ghosts, for example.
One such story is that you shouldn't
look into the waters of the reservoir,
when the moon is full.
Because when you turn away,
and your reflection will take on a life of its own.
It seems to me
as if until now I was somewhere at the bottom of a reservoir.
Now
It's time to come to the surface.
I could have waited for the elder.
Looks like it was pressed hard.
Stand. The needy is on that side.
There is something that I have hidden from you.
Something I kept secret from everyone.
What only Her Majesty and I know.
During the full moon, werewolves turn
into wolves.
However, we all
We know very well that the full moon is just an excuse,
to release the wolf that has always been hidden inside.
What is it, a chamber pot?
It’s no good doing things in such beauty.
Tango?
Have you come to your senses?
Take me to Her Majesty's chambers.
I will guard her personally.
Queen?
What a bastard, why are you offending my poor king?
I bring retribution
in the name of the moon!
I only drank a little
and grace became like a potato.
Come on, get up. Still good?
Why did you expose yourself to attack?
There he is!
Let's forget about distancing today.
Your Majesty.
Are you okay?
You can't help but get into trouble.
It would be very unfortunate if you forgot last night.
You can always buy a name plate.
Who knows? Suddenly he is under someone else's guise
came here to start a rebellion.
It's all my fault.
I had to keep my mouth shut.
Let's make a little excursion.
Ingratiates himself with the Kims
that almost his entire family was slaughtered.
Speak, but don't talk.
-Who else are you?
-I
I am a member of the king's fan club.